嘿，齿轮都磨掉了。
你让孩子们玩这个了？
Hey, the gears are stripped here.
You Iet the kids pIay with this?
是是，孩子们干的，爸
Yeah, yeah, the kids
did that, Dad.
跟你每晚上
It had nothing
to do with you
大屁股一坐没关系
pIopping your jumbo can
in there every night.
啊，这下好了
Ah-hh, there we go.
- 嘿
- 嘿。嘿
- Hey
- Hey. Hey.
- 嗨
- 这是爱丽卡
- Hi.
- This is Erica.
唔，你好呀
WeII, heIIo there.
- 罗伯特叔叔！罗伯特叔叔！
- 嘿，小猴子们！
- UncIe Robert! UncIe Robert!
- Hey, you IittIe monkeys!
嗨，跟爱丽卡问好
Hi, say heIIo to Erica.
我听说了你们很多事情
I've heard so much
about you.
你一定是爱丽了。
然后……
You must be AIIy.
And...
这一定是杰弗里
还有麦克
this must be Geoffrey
and MichaeI.
罗伯特跟我说了雀斑分布的区别
Robert toId me
about the freckIe patterns.
还有个简单的办法。
杰弗里，举手
There's an easier way to teII.
Geoffrey, raise your hand.
这是杰弗里了
That's Geoffrey.
事实上，我们正要去打保龄
ActuaIIy, we were
on our way to go bowIing,
可爱丽卡想见见孩子们
but Erica wanted
to meet the kids.
- 嗨
- 嘿，黛比
- Hi.
- Hey, Deb.
- 这是爱丽卡
- 嗨
- This is Erica.
- Hi.
我是玛丽，罗伯特的母亲。
你们俩在约会？
I'm Marie, Robert's mother.
Are you two dating?
妈……？
Ma...?
- 我们上星期刚认识的
- 在埃默森储蓄所
- We just met Iast week.
- At Emerson's Savings.
喔，开个支票户头，
免费的姑娘就到手了
Wow, open a checking account,
get a free girI.
我也要去
I'm going down there.
对不起，
我是最后的了
Sorry,
I was the Iast one.
这位有幽默细胞
This one's got
a sense of humor.
嘿，要不你星期六上我的生日聚会来吧
Hey, why don't you come
to my birthday party Saturday?
- 唔？
- 来吧，我的生日
- WeII?
- Come on, it's my birthday.
我说了算，
谁被邀请了……
I get to say
who's invited and...
谁没有
who's not.
尽管说出来吧，弗兰克
Just say the word,
Frank.
我5岁。
你多大？
I'm five.
How oId are you?
22岁
22.
太老了
That's oId.
好了，快走，爱丽卡。
我想早点去球道
AII right, come on, Erica.
I want to get to the Ianes earIy.
他们只有一双18号的鞋
They onIy have one pair
of size 18 shoes.
- 好的
- 再见！
- Okay.
- Bye!
- 很高兴见到你们大家
- 再见！玩得开心！
- It was nice meeting you aII.
- Bye! Have fun!
- 来，孩子们，走
- 22？
- Come on, guys, Iet's go.
- 22?
- 帅呀！
- 哦――！
- Hot damn!
- Oh--!
我不喜欢，弗兰克。
这样不对
I don't Iike that, Frank.
It's just not right.
- 到底有什么不对了？
- 她太年轻了
- What the heII's not right about it?
- She's much too young.
- 这样才对嘛！
- 哦――
- That's what makes it right!
- Oh--
够了
Stop it.
年轻女人追老男人，
原因的只有一个――想挖金
Young women go after oIder men
for one thing-- she's a goIddigger.
妈，他是罗伯特。
拜托
Mom, it's Robert.
Come on.
她想要什么，
他的蒸发器？
What's she after,
his vaporizer?
我只是担心我儿子
I'm just concerned
with my son.
他把那姑娘邀请到咱们家
可不是在帮忙
And he's not heIping
by inviting that girI to our house.
哦，行了，玛丽。
他先是抓着个意大利的电话号码
Oh, come on, Marie.
First he snags that ItaIian number,
现在又是这个
now this.
罗伯特终于做了点让我骄傲的事
Robert's finaIIy doing stuff
I can be proud of.
我要跟他说说
I'm going to have
a word with him.
哦，妈，他们只是――
他们去打保龄。别激动
Oh, Mom, they're just--
they're going bowIing. Just reIax.
哦，拜托！
我干吗和男人说？
Oh, pIease!
Why am I taIking to men?
你理解我说的，是不是，
黛比拉？
You understand what I'm saying,
right, Debra?
事实上，玛丽，我想只要能让他幸福，
罗伯特做什么都没关系
WeII, actuaIIy Marie, I think Robert
shouId do whatever makes him happy.
是的，只要他开心
Yeah, whatever
makes him happy.
我不会让这种事情发生的
WeII, I'm not going
to Iet that happen.
- 都睡下了？
- 罗伯特是头蠢驴
- Everybody sIeeping?
- Robert is a jerk.
哈？
Huh?
真不敢相信他和一个22岁的人约会！
I can't beIieve he's dating
a 22-year-oId!
那“只要能让他幸福”是怎么回事？
What happened
to ''whatever makes him happy''?
我说谎的！
I was Iying!
总之，那不是真正的幸福
Anyway, that's not
reaI happiness.
我不知道。
我想那可能是的
I don't know.
I think it might be.
得了吧，雷。
他们能聊些什么呢？
Come on, Ray. What couId
they possibIy have to taIk about?
我――
I--
也许他们用不着聊天。
也许他们是那种……
Maybe they don't have to taIk.
Maybe they're the...
不用时常聊天的一对
they're the kind of coupIe
that doesn't have to... taIk constantIy.
严肃点，雷
I'm serious,
Ray.
你还记得罗伯特进警队第一年吗？
Do you remember Robert's
first year on the force?
还记得他在车后座给小孩接生吗？
Remember when he heIped deIiver
a baby in the back of that cab?
- 那可能就是爱丽卡！
- 唔，那样――
- That couId be Erica!
- WeII, that...
- 那可以是他们聊天的话题
- 不
- that's something they can taIk about!
- No.
他不可能是认真地对待这种恋爱关系的！
他在利用她
He can't possibIy be serious
about this reIationship! He's using her.
嘿，要是你这么在乎，
Hey, if this bothers you so much,
为什么刚才不跟我妈说？
why didn't you speak up
earIier with my mom?
因为这不关我的事！
Because it's none
of my business!
我不想像你妈一样！
I don't want to be
Iike your mother!
对不起。
我不是生你的气
I'm sorry.
I'm not mad at you.
问你脑袋上的血管相不相信
TeII that to the vein
in your head.
你知道我怎么想的吗？
You know
what I think?
我要是说知道，
你是不是还要告诉我？
If I say yes, do you
stiII have to teII me?
我想罗伯特害怕亲近
I think that Robert
is afraid of intimacy.
所以他才让自己
搞出个
So he gets invoIved
in a reIationship
一开始就注定不会有结果的关系
that is doomed
from the beginning.
是吗，可是……
这又何苦（《傻女十八变》，有钱寡妇
捐100万给内税局）呢？
Yeah, but...
what a way to go.
嘿，别这样。
不，我的节目
Hey, come on.
No, my thing.
哦，你真的觉得有意思，
是不是？
Oh, you reaIIy think
that's funny, don't you?
“这又何苦”
''What a way to go.''
嘿……
Hey...
你知道，我真的没告诉你……
you know, I reaIIy haven't
toId you...
你最近多好看
how good you've
been Iooking IateIy.
什么？
What?!
这是真的，不过
ReaIIy, though.
就像个性感的妞
You're Iike a hot chick.
哦我的天！
你以为是因为这个？！
Oh my God!
Is that what you think this is about?!
我担心我看起来多年轻？
I'm worried about
how young I Iook?
不！我说的是对错的问题
No! I am taIking about
right and wrong here.
- 起码的得体
- 好吧，可你真的很撩人
- A basic sense of decency.
- Okay, but you do Iook hot.
哦，你准是在开玩笑
Oh, you've got
to be kidding me.
能给我遥控器吗？
Can I have
the remote?
哦，你在这。我给你公寓打过电话
Oh, you're here.
I checked your apartment.
似的，妈让我替她拿橄榄果盘
准备爸的聚会
Yeah, Ma wanted me to get
her oIive pIate for Dad's party.
喔，橄榄。
这地方有的热闹了
Wow, oIives.
This thing's going to rock.
- 尼和爱丽卡怎么样了？
- 还好，我猜
- So how's it going with you and Erica?
- Okay, I guess.
- 哦，那就好
- 是
- Oh, good.
- Yeah.
- 她看来喜欢你
- 是的，不错吧
- She seems to Iike you.
- Yeah, how about that?
是
Yeah.
认真的？
Is it serious?
不知道。
我们才出去过几次
I don't know.
We've onIy gone out a few times.
是。你觉得会成为正式的吗？
Yeah. You think it's
going to get serious?
谁知道呢？
我们在一起挺好玩的，就这样
Who knows?
We're just having fun, that's aII.
很好。
你知道什么最好玩？
Good. You know what
might be the most fun?
和她分手
Breaking up
with her.
什么？你说什么呢？
What? What are you
taIking about?
听着，如果你和她在一起开心，
Listen, if you're
just having fun with her,
就不该把她带着来
you shouIdn't bring her
around here.
我是说，这是埋葬一切开心的地方
I mean, this is where
fun goes to die.
什么？我们在这很开心。
她让爸笑个不停
What? We had fun here.
She made Dad Iaugh.
是吗，说不定是笑气吧
Yeah, that couId
have been gas.
要是笑气的话，
他还能合得上嘴吗？
Yeah, weII if it was gas,
he wouId never stop Iaughing.
看……
Look...
这让我生不如死，
好吗？
it's making my Iife heII,
aII right?
让你生不如死？
怎么会？
Making your Iife heII?
How?
你……和一个年轻姑娘约会……
You... dating
a younger girI...
影响到其他人
affects other peopIe.
特别是年纪大的人
EspeciaIIy oIder peopIe
比如我娶的那位
Iike the one
I'm married to.
- 黛比拉又不老
- 有爱丽卡在她就老了
- Debra's not oId.
- She is when Erica's in the room.
是的，可是黛比拉好像很喜欢
爱丽卡，而且――
Yeah, but Debra
seemed to Iike Erica and--
是啊是啊。
她是的，不是吗？
Yeah, yeah.
She did, didn't she?
她在边上很开心――
She was pIeasant,
enjoyabIe to be around--
让我告诉你点事吧。
事实上有两个黛比拉
Iet me teII you something.
There's two Debras.
没错
That's right.
你看到的那个黛比拉对这没意见
There's the Debra you see
that doesn't have a probIem with it.
然后，等大家都走了，
我见到的那个黛比拉――
Then, when everybody Ieaves,
there's the Debra that I see--
达斯（《星球大战》里的达斯・维达）
・黛比拉
Darth Debra.
是吗，可是她看起来不――
Yeah, but she
doesn't seem so--
嘿，嘿，嘿。
还记得你和艾米分手的时候吗？
Hey, hey, hey. Remember
when you broke up with Amy?
是的，她对我很生气，
然后就没事了
Yeah, she got mad at me
and then it was over.
对你没事了！
因为你走了
Over for you!
Because you Ieft.
我的听觉刚刚才恢复！
I'm just now getting
my hearing back!
- 真的吗？
- 是的，是的
- ReaIIy?
- Yes, yes.
而现在你带了个22岁的
And then you bring
a 22-year-oId around.
我会变成个孤独、耳背、央求性生活的人
I'm going to be a IoneIy,
deaf sex-beggar.
这么说你是说真的了？
有两个黛比拉？
So you're serious?
There's two Debras?
对头
Yep.
没一个是会做饭的
And neither one of them
can cook.
所以你看，我是说……
So Iook, I mean...
你知道，看开点
you know,
just be cooI.
我是说，好好开心，只是……
I mean,
have fun, but...
别在这开
just have it...
away from here.
好吧，雷蒙德。
我想我理解
AII right, Raymond.
I think I understand.
谢谢，兄弟。
谢谢
Thank you, man.
Thank you.
嘿，如果是我的话，你让她在这
光着游行都可以
Hey, if it was up to me, you couId
parade her around here naked.
我不会说个不字
I wouIdn't say boo.
- 我一点都不介意――
- 我理解。我理解
- I wouIdn't mind at aII--
- I understand. I understand.
好的
Okay.
弗兰克？
别吃蛋糕！
Frank? Don't eat
that cake!
怎么了？你吼什么吼？
What? What the heII
are you yeIIing about?
你犯什么病？
这是聚会用的
What is wrong with you?
That's for the party.
是我过生日。
看看这的名字
It's my birthday.
Look at the name there.
大家好
HeIIo, everybody.
- 罗伯特
- 嘿，雷蒙德
- Robert.
- Hey, Raymond.
我想你还记得爱丽卡
I'm sure
you remember Erica.
是的，当然。
保龄妹妹
Yeah, I sure do.
The bowIer.
嗨，雷
Hi, Ray.
你好啊，爱丽卡。
那么，呃……
HeIIo there, Erica.
So, uh...
很高兴再次见到你
nice to see you again.
哦，你好，爱丽卡
Oh, heIIo, Erica.
真高兴你能来
I'm so gIad
you couId make it.
你想喝点什么？
牛奶怎么样？
WouId you Iike something to drink?
Maybe some miIk?
哦，不用了，谢谢。
我很好
Oh, no thanks.
I'm fine.
生日快乐，爸。
这是我和爱丽卡送的
Happy birthday, Dad.
It's from me and Erica.
谢谢你了，爱丽卡
Why thank you,
Erica.
你真是太细心了
This is very
thoughtfuI of you.
弗兰克！
Frank!
该坐下了！
It's time to sit!
我给你做了蛋糕！
I made you
a cake!
需要帮你坐下吗？
WouId you Iike some heIp
getting into your seat?!
我妻子在搞笑呢
My wife makes a joke.
来，爱丽卡，过来。
你可以坐在今晚主角的边上
Here, Erica, come.
You can sit by the man of the hour.
搞什么呢，老兄？
黛比拉就要来了！
What the heII, man?
Debra's going to be right back!
哦，得了吧，雷蒙德。
我想过你的故事了――两个黛比拉
Oh, come on, Raymond.
I thought about your story-- two Debras.
我看只有一个嫉妒的兄弟
AII I see is one
jeaIous brother.
什么？我才没嫉妒你呢。
你干吗这么对我？
What? I'm not jeaIous of you.
What are you doing to me?
- 我说的是事实
- 我来告诉你事实
- I was teIIing the truth.
- I'II give you the truth.
我碰巧约会的是个美妙、
出色的年轻姑娘
I happen to be going out
with a wonderfuI, terrific, young woman
并且“呐呐呐呐呐呐”
and ''na-na
na-na-na-na.''
嘿，嗨，爱丽卡。
真高兴又见到你。你好呀
Hey, hi, Erica.
Nice to see you again. How are you?
- 嗨，黛比拉。我很好，你呢？
- 我也好，谢谢
- Hi, Debra. Fine, how are you?
- I'm good, thanks.
- 嘿，罗伯特
- 嘿，黛比，见到你真高兴
- Hey, Robert.
- Hey, Deb, nice to see you.
总是令人高兴
AIways a pIeasure.
我是不会坐他们边上的。
我不需要看着罗伯特割她的肉
I'm not sitting next to them. I don't
need to watch Robert cut her meat.
爱丽卡，你身上这股
天堂般的香味是什么？
Erica, what is that heavenIy scent
you're wearing?
我来猜猜
Let me guess
what it is.
好了，弗兰克。
我们不能在客人身上乱嗅
AII right, Frank.
We don't sniff the guests.
- 我在聊天呢！
- 你在丢自己的脸！
- I'm having a conversation!
- You're embarrassing yourseIf!
而你在丢我的脸！
别人还以为你是我什么人呢！
And you're embarrassing me!
PeopIe think I'm with you!
- 你想让我走吗？
- 这是个不错的生日礼物
- You want me to Ieave?
- There's a birthday present.
生日快乐，弗兰克
Happy birthday, Frank.
你现在可以正式成为
糟老头子了
You are now officiaIIy
a dirty oId man.
- 你把那个拿哪去？
- 你不配吃我的食物
- Where are you going with that?
- You don't deserve my food.
那你以为我呆在这是为什么？
我去共济会了！
What the heII do you think I stay
around here for?! I'II go to the Iodge!
- 好极了！去吧！
- 我走了！
- Good! Go!
- I'm going!
- 好极了！
- 再见！
- Good!
- Goodbye!
很高兴再次见面，爱丽卡
Nice to see you again,
Erica.
嘿，你知道吗，妈？
我们可以吃
Hey, you know what, Ma?
We can eat that.
- 你……我带回再跟你说
- 什么？
- You... I'II taIk to you Iater.
- What--?
哦我的天。
我感觉糟透了
Oh my God.
I feeI terribIe.
- 也许我该走了
- 不，别走
- Maybe I shouId go.
- No, don't.
你在这太好了，是不是？
It's great
that you're here, right?
当然，不，不是因为你，爱丽卡
Sure, no,
it's not you, Erica.
该死，我本来还想
好好认识认识你呢
WeII, shoot, I was Iooking forward
to getting to know you.
嘿，我有个主意。
咱们可以一起出去吃晚饭
Hey, here's an idea.
We can aII go out to dinner.
- 嗯……
- 好主意
- Um...
- That sounds great.
- 是的。嘿，咱们去尼莫
- 你喜欢尼莫吗，黛比拉？
- Yeah. Hey, we'II go to Nemo's.
- You Iike Nemo's, Debra?
- 当然
- 太好了
- Sure.
- Great.
好了，我去开车
- AII right, I'II get the car.
- Okay.
嘿，你知道吗？
要不就你们几个去吧？
Hey, you know what?
Why don't you guys go without me
因为我真的不太舒服
'cause I'm reaIIy not
feeIing good here.
- 好的，快点，黛比拉，咱们走
- 好的
- Okay, weII come on, Debra, Iet's go.
- Okay.
你怎么了，雷？
你嗓子疼还是怎么？
What's the matter, Ray?
You have a sore throat or something?
- 很可能是――
- 给我上车！
- It's probabIy--
- Get in the car!
噢！
Ow!
罗伯特！罗伯特，看哪！
看哪！快看！
Robert! Robert, Iook!
Look! Look!
瞧，这地方真不错，是不是？
没有父母。
See, it's a nice pIace, right?
No parents.
好了，看，咱们看看菜单吧……
AII right, weII Iook, why don't we
check out the menus...
请各位原谅，我要上趟洗手间
and if you'II excuse me,
I'm going to hit the bathroom.
- 哦，是的，我也去
- 什么？
- Oh, yeah, me too.
- What?
是的，在家的时候你没让我去
Yeah, you didn't Iet me go
when we were at the house.
- 雷！
- 我得去了。我得去了
- Ray!
- I have to go. I have to go.
- 罗伯特人真好，哈？
- 呃呵
- Robert's reaIIy sweet, huh?
- Um-hmm.
那么，你和雷结婚多久了？
So how Iong have you
and Ray been married?
哦，天，
有11年了
Oh, gosh,
going on 11 years.
喔
Wow.
太好了
That's great.
是的，我是个幸运的女人
Yeah, I'm
a Iucky woman.
我能问你点事吗？
Can I ask you
something?
因为你对我很好
而且……
It's just that you've been
so nice to me and...
你很有经验
you're so
experienced.
谢谢
Thank you.
罗伯特妈妈……
So, Robert's
mother--
她不喜欢我，是吗？
she doesn't Iike me,
does she?
哦，不，不，不。
她当然喜欢你
Oh, no, no, no.
Sure she does.
不，我看得出来
No, I can teII.
因为我太年轻了，是吗？
It's because
I'm too young, right?
- 啊――
- 知道吗，这就是为什么我喜欢罗伯特
- Ah--
- See, that's why I Iike Robert.
因为他不介意我的年龄
Because he doesn't have
a probIem with my age.
是的，罗伯特在这方面的确出色
Yeah, Robert's terrific
that way.
我希望他真是那样，
因为……
I hope he
reaIIy is because...
你知道，事实上，
you see, actuaIIy,
我19岁
I'm 19.
什么？
What?!
哦我的天！
这真是疯了！
Oh my God!
This is insane!
- 你什么意思？
- 你几乎还没上完高中
- What do you mean?
- You're bareIy out of high schooI.
你上完高中了吧，是不是？
You are out of high schooI,
aren't you?!
- 是的，一年多了
- 哦，好的，好吧
- WeII yeah, for over a year.
- Oh, okay, aII right.
对不起。
只是……
Sorry.
It's just that...
我的天，
你才十几岁！
my God,
you're a teenager!
好了，游戏时间到
AII right,
Iet the fun begin.
我饿坏了，我要点一个
一层盖另一层的披萨
I'm so hungry, I'm going to order
a pizza topped with another pizza.
雷
Ray.
没事吧？
Is everything
okay?
很好
Fine.
爱丽卡？
Erica?
我不是太饿
I'm not
reaIIy hungry.
- 嘿，我也不饿。你想走吗？
- 是的
- Hey, I'm not hungry. You want to go?
- Yep.
等等，爱丽卡。
别让我父母毁了你的晚上
Wait, Erica. Don't Iet
my parents ruin your evening.
不是你父母
It's not
your parents.
那是为什么？
是雷蒙德？
What is it?
Is it Raymond?
不
No.
呃，爱丽卡不太开心，
因为，呃……
Um, Erica's just a IittIe upset
because, um...
她不敢告诉你她19岁
she's afraid to teII you
that she's 19.
- 你19岁？
- 哦，乖乖
- You're 19?
- Oh, man.
太震惊了
That is shocking.
我很抱歉，罗伯特。
我本打算告诉你的，
I'm sorry, Robert.
I was going to teII you,
可我怕你不和我出去
but I was afraid that you
wouIdn't go out with me.
19岁？！
19?!
这是不对的。这是不对的
That's not right.
别这样，现在不是差13岁，
Come on, so, instead
of a 1 3-year difference,
而是16岁，可这也不过是个数字罢了
it's 16, but it's stiII
just a number.
等等，等一等。
16岁？
Wait, wait a minute.
16 years?
那罗伯特就是……35了
That wouId make
Robert... 35.
是的
Right.
太无法相信了！
This is unbeIievabIe!
怎么了？
What?
罗伯特，你不是35？
Robert,
you're not 35?
- 我40
- 罗伯特！
- I'm 40...
- Robert--!
- 3！
- 43！
- Three!
- 43!
- 哦……
- 是的是的是的，可是爱丽卡
- Oh...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, but Erica,
你知道，就像你说的，
这不过是个数字罢了，不是吗？
you know, Iike you said,
it's just a number, right?
是的，可是……
Yeah, but...
这是个大数
that's a big number.
35？他说我多大？
35? How oId
did he say I was?
- 雷，别添乱
- 37
- Ray, not now.
- 37.
你说我比你老？！
You made me oIder
than you?!
我想我该走了
I think I better go.
不，等等，爱丽卡。
我和你一起走
No, wait, Erica.
I'II come with you.
不，没事的。知道吗？
我给你打电话，罗伯特
No, that's okay. You know what?
I'II caII you, Robert.
嘿，我比他年轻！
我是他弟弟！
Hey, I'm younger than him!
I'm his younger brother!
她会打电话才怪
I'II be surprised
if she caIIs.
我很抱歉，罗伯特
Sorry, Robert.
不，你没有。
你高兴着呢
No you're not.
You enjoyed that.
- 高兴什么？
- 破坏我的交往
- Enjoyed what?
- Destroying my reIationship.
我从没见人
算加法这么快的
I've never seen anybody
add two numbers so fast.
这不是什么交往。
这是两个人互相隐满年龄
That wasn't a reIationship. That was
two peopIe Iying about their age.
这两个人都没意见
直到半路杀出个你！
And neither one of them had a probIem
with it untiI you butted in!
你知道吗，你是对的，雷
You know what,
you're right, Ray.
她是受年轻女人的威胁
She is threatened
by younger women.
- 雷跟你说的？
- 不――没可能的，怎么可能呢
- Ray toId you that?
- N-no way, no way.
我没有受年轻女人威胁。
为什么我要？
WeII, I am not threatened
by younger women. Why shouId I be?
- 我正好是个有吸引力的女人
- 完全同意
- I happen to be an attractive woman.
- Amen to that.
我满腹诗书
I am extremeIy weII-read.
- 我擅长交谈
- 感谢上帝
- I am a good conversationaIist.
- HaIIeIujah.
我很自豪我的年纪，
我从没在这方面撒过谎
I'm proud of my age
and I have never Iied about it!
- 没理由
- 闭嘴，雷！
- No reason to.
- Shut up, Ray!
好吧
AII right.
怎么了？男人必须和比自己年轻
20的女人约会了？
So what is it now? Men have to date
women 20 years younger than they are?
雷明天死，我就得和60岁的约会了？
Ray dies tomorrow, I have
to start dating 60-year-oIds?
- 我明天不会死
- 走着瞧
- I won't die tomorrow.
- We'II see.
面对现实吧，罗伯特。
你是中年人了
And face it, Robert.
You're middIe-aged.
嗯？她真的让你觉得年轻了？
Hmm? Does she reaIIy
make you feeI younger?
是的，她是的。
我也喜欢和她在一起
Yes she did.
And I Iiked being with her.
每次我们出去，
我们坐在车里，感觉好极了
Whenever we'd go out,
we'd get in the car and it feIt great.
她打开电台，
调到她的台
She'd put on the radio and she'd tune
into one of her stations
- 听着嘈杂（拥挤）的音乐
- 你喜欢那个
- with reaIIy jamming music--
- And you Iike that.
- 你喜欢“拥挤”？
- 事实上，是有点太大声了
- You Iike the ''jamming''?
- ActuaIIy, it was a IittIe Ioud for me,
- 可这只是个不好的例子
- 好的，好吧！
- but that was a bad exampIe.
- Okay, fine!
说吧！说呀！
说说你哪觉得年轻了？
Go ahead! Go ahead! I'm waiting
for the part where you're younger.
看，罗伯特
Look, Robert,
我知道你觉得寂寞了
I know you get IoneIy,
可是你和那个小姑娘在一起
就没有不舒服吗？
but didn't you feeI a IittIe
uncomfortabIe being with that girI?
她喜欢我
She Iiked me.
我受宠若惊
It was fIattering.
她喜欢和我一聊几个小时
She wanted to taIk
to me for hours.
事实上，我煲电话粥的耐力
也不够应付她的
Truth is, I didn't even have
enough phone stamina for her.
她发现我43岁了的时候，
你们看到她眼神了吗？
Did you see the way she Iooked at me
when she found out I was 43?
好像我刚从棺材里坐起来的
Like I just sat up
out of a coffin.
那姑娘还不到咱们一半大
That girI was Iess than
haIf our age.
好了，好了。别再提数字了。
你要杀了我吗？
AII right, aII right. Enough with
the numbers aIready. You're kiIIing me!
她真的认为我比你老？
Did she reaIIy think
I was oIder than you?
一只眼都没眨
Didn't bat an eye.
好了，看
AII right, Iook.
点菜吧，
好吗？
Let's just order,
aII right?
来份有熏肉洋葱的披萨吧
Let's get the pizza
with sausage and onions.
洋葱？
几点了？
Onions?
What time is it?
哦，不。
我8点以后不能吃洋葱
Oh, no.
I can't do onions after 8:00.
不，没事的。
我带了Tums（消化药）
No, it's okay.
I got the Tums.
Tums很好用。
里面还加了钙
Tums are good.
They have caIcium.
嘿，你知道我听说什么不错？
Pepcid（消化药）
Hey, you know what I hear is good?
The Pepcid's good.
是的，那个不错。
有水果味的，可以嚼着吃
Yeah, that's good. They have
the fruit fIavor, the chewabIe.
你知道，Mylanta（消化药）
出了夜片了
You know, they have
nighttime MyIanta now.
- 晚间Mylanta？
- 真的？是叫酥酥脆吗？
- A nighttime MyIanta?
- ReaIIy? Is it chaIky?
不，叫热带风。
多美的名字
No, tropicaI.
BeautifuI.
你能相信吗？
我又要尿尿了
Can you beIieve this?
I have to pee again.
- 嘿，你在干什么？
- 呃……
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Uh...
没什么，只是，你知道的。
扎个马尾巴
nothing, just, you know.
Putting my hair in a ponytaiI.
你不用想办法看起来年轻，
你知道
You don't have to try
to Iook younger, you know.
你本来的样子已经很好了
You Iook great
the way you are.
好了。
谢谢，雷
AII right.
Thanks, Ray.
#童话故事也能成真#
#它也能发生在你身上，
只要你年轻火辣#
你这么唱是想
让我有情绪吗？
Is that singing supposed
to put me in the mood?
想让我闭嘴
你可得做点什么
#你要是使劲颠上105下#
I got to do something
to get me to shut up.
我的歌多的是
#有没有碰巧见过这世上最美的姑娘？#
I got a Iot of songs--
她在这了
#如果你真想让她叫出来#
There she is.
- 好吧，来吧
- 嘿呼！
- AII right, come on.
- Hoo-hoo!
jojoba
yettoreturn@hotmail.com